来自我们 AFA 选择部分的另一则说明，很高兴与我们的朋友 Nahuel Molina 一起来到 AFA Predio
Another note from our AFA selection section, it is a pleasure to be here at the AFA Predio with our friend Nahuel Molina
otra nota más de nuestra sección AFA selección es un placer estar aquí en el AFA Predio con nuestro amigo Nahuel Molina
欢迎老师，您好吗？
Welcome teacher, how are you doing?
Bienvenido maestro, ¿cómo le va?
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
Muchas gracias.
感谢您来到 Random Infoboy。
Thank you for being here at Random Infoboy.
Gracias por estar acá en Random Infoboy.
一切都好吗？
All good?
¿Todo bien?
好，很好，说实话我很高兴。
Good, very good, the truth is that I am very happy.
Bien, muy bien, la verdad que muy contento.
感谢Dadi，感谢Nico，媒体，所有为我们提供这些笔记的美丽人士。
Thanks to Dadi, thanks to Nico, press, all the beautiful people who have provided us with these notes with all of you.
Gracias a Dadi, gracias a Nico, prensa, toda la gente hermosa que nos ha facilitado estas notas con todos ustedes.
对我来说这是一种乐趣。
For me it is a pleasure.
Para mí es un placer.
您在选拔场地感觉如何？
What is it like for you to be at the Selection Grounds?
¿Para vos cómo es estar en el Predio de la Selección?
这是一种荣幸，这是一种自豪，我已经有宾至如归的感觉了。
It is an honor, it is a pride, I already felt at home.
Es un honor, es un orgullo, ya te sentí como en tu casa.
感觉怎么样？
What is the feeling like?
¿Cómo es la sensación?
现在我每次来，此时此刻我都为自己说话，但我认为绝大多数
Now every time I come, I speak for myself at this moment, but I think the vast majority
Ahora que cada vez que vengo, hablo por mí en este momento, pero creo que la gran mayoría
很荣幸来到这里，进入场地，穿上我们的衣服。
It is a privilege to be here, to enter the premises, to put on our clothes.
Es un privilegio estar acá, entrar en el predio, ponernos la ropa.
他们说的话似乎是重复的，但它很美丽，非常好。
It seems repetitive that they are saying it, but it is beautiful, it is very nice.
Por ahí parece repetitivo que lo van diciendo, pero es hermoso, es muy lindo.
他们如何接待你，他们接待你的愿望......
how they receive you, with the desire they receive you...
cómo te reciben, con las ganas que te reciben...
每个人都会接待您，所以很高兴一直在酒店里。
with the predisposition that everyone receives you, so it is very nice to be here on the premises always.
con la predisposición que te reciben todos, así que es muy lindo estar acá en el predio siempre.
你想念你的房子吗？
And do you miss your house?
y a tu casa extrañas vas?
当我可以去的时候，事实是我很难去。
And when I can, the truth is that it is difficult for me to go.
Y cuando puedo, la verdad que se me complica ir.
当我加入国家队时，这是不可能的，因为他们不给我时间。
When I come with the national team, impossible, because they don't give me the time.
Cuando vengo con la selección, imposible, porque no me dan los tiempos.
但只要我能去，我就会去，或者我的家人也会去。
But whenever I can go I go or my family comes there.
Pero siempre que puedo ir voy o por ahí viene mi familia.
你的家人在吗？
Is your family there?
¿Tu familia está allá?
是的，是的，我的家人住在那边，在 Embalse，在科尔多瓦。
Yes, yes, my family lives all over there, in Embalse, in Córdoba.
Sí, sí, mi familia vive en todo ahí, en Embalse, en Córdoba.
里奥特塞罗水库？
Río Tercero reservoir?
¿Enbalse Río Tercero?
正确的。
Correct.
Correcto.
那里有很多巴斯克斯球员。
There have been many Vázquez players there.
Ha habido muchos jugadores del Vázquez ahí.
那里的巴斯克斯非常好。
Very good Vázquez there.
Muy buen Vázquez ahí.
当然是米兰人。
The Milanese, surely.
El milanesio, seguramente.
显然这不是我的事。
It's not my thing, obviously.
No es lo mío, obviamente.
你还参加过哪些其他运动？
What other sports did you play?
¿Qué otros deportes jugaste?
足球。
Soccer.
Fútbol.
只是足球。
Just football.
Solo fútbol.
篮球、网球、父母？
Basketball, tennis, parents?
¿Básquetes, tenis, padres?
没什么，没什么。
Nothing, nothing.
Nada, nada.
总是？
Always?
¿Siempre?
是的，总是如此。
Yes, always.
Sí, desde siempre.
我父亲的家人，所有的球迷，都在那里踢球。
My dad's side of the family, all football fans, all played there.
La familia de parte de mi viejo, todos futboleros, jugaron todos ahí.
在科尔多瓦，在那里的联赛中。
in Córdoba, in the leagues there.
en Córdoba, en las ligas de ahí.
你没有机会成为一名足球运动员吗？
Didn't you have a chance to be a footballer?
¿No tenías chance de que no haces de ser futbolista?
不。
No.
你还擅长其他方面吗？
And are you good for anything else?
¿Y sos bueno para otra cosa?
在生活中。
in life.
en la vida.
煮得很好，进展顺利，伙计……我还能说什么？
It cooks well, it goes well mate... What else can I say?
Cocina bien, se va bueno mate... ¿Qué otra cosa puedo decir?
这件事我做得很好。
I do this well.
Esto yo lo hago bien.
嗯，我陪着。
Nah, I'll accompany.
Nah, acompaño.
我是一个好伴侣。
I am a good companion.
Soy buen acompañante.
对于每个人来说。
For everyone.
Para todos.
不错。
Not bad.
No está mal.
你要懂得陪伴。
You have to know how to accompany.
Hay que saber acompañar.
为大家陪伴。
Accompany for everyone.
Acompañe para todos.
你必须有人陪伴。
You have to be accompanied.
Hay que ser acompañado.
我从很小的时候就开始了足球、足球、足球，所以从那时起我就改变了……
I started from a very young age and it was always football, football and football, so that's when I changed...
Desde muy chico arranqué y siempre fue fútbol, fútbol y fútbol, entonces por ahí cambiar la...
球很难。
The ball is difficult.
La bocha es difícil.
你今天几岁了？
How old are you today?
¿Qué edad tenés hoy?
26年。
26 years.
26 años.
26.
你知道吗？
Are you aware?
¿Sos consciente?
我们正在与亚历克西斯和塔利亚交谈，塔利亚年纪稍大一些。
We were talking with Alexis, with Taglia, Taglia a little older.
Estuvimos hablando con Alexis, con Taglia, Taglia un poquito más grande.
但你是否意识到，你们已经到了选拔的一个阶段，突然你们都一起获胜了？
But are you aware that you reached a stage in the selection where suddenly you all won together?
¿Pero sos consciente que ustedes llegaron a una etapa de la selección donde de repente ganaron todos juntos?
两次美洲杯世界冠军入围决赛，这并不常见。
finalist of the world champion of two American Cups and that is not usual.
finalísima campeona del mundo dos copas américa y que no es lo habitual.
我不知道我是否意识到，但是...
I don't know if I'm aware, but...
No sé si soy consciente, pero...
显然这不平常，也不正常。
Obviously it is not usual and it is not normal.
Obviamente que no es lo habitual y no es lo normal.
我是第一次来。
I had to come for the first time.
A mí me tocó venir por primera vez.
参加美洲杯并赢得胜利。
Go to the Copa América and win it.
Ir a la Copa América y ganarla.
这太不可思议了。
It was incredible.
Fue increíble.
带着冠军，带着球队所拥有的一切。
With a championship, with everything that the team had been.
Con campeonato, con todo lo que venía siendo la selección.
前几年他们到达了，但没有得到它。
The previous years they arrived and they were not given it.
los años anteriores que llegaban y por ahí no se les daba.
对于我第一次有机会来，说实话，我以为我什至不会去美洲杯。
For me to have the possibility of coming for the first time, I thought I wasn't even going to the Copa América, honestly.
que a mí tener la posibilidad de venir por primera vez, que yo pensé que ni iba a la Copa América, sinceramente.
但不，因为你有信心，但你说不，我知道什么。
But no, because you had faith, but you said no, what do I know.
Pero no, porque te tenías fe, pero decías no, qué sé yo.
但没有，因为几个来得比较久的同事已经来了。
But no, because several colleagues who had been coming for a longer time were already coming.
Pero no, porque ya venían varios compañeros que ya venían hace ya más tiempo.
那时我没有想到我没有那么多的可能性
time then I didn't have in my thoughts I didn't have that much possibility
tiempo entonces yo no tenía en mi pensamiento no tenía tanta posibilidad
然后事情发生了，我们成为了冠军，继续前进后，我成为了世界杯决赛的冠军。
Then it happened, we became champions and after continuing to come, I became champion of the World Cup final.
Después se dio, salimos campeones y después seguir viniendo, salí campeón de la finalísima del Mundial.
这太不可思议了。
It was incredible.
Fue increíble.
现在我认为我还没有完全意识到......
Now that I don't think I'm fully aware of...
Ahora que no creo ser el todo consciente de...
不，因为上帝希望坏事永远不会到来，或者它不会像之前的干旱那样来得那么久，但当然是突然的……
No, because God wants that the bad thing never comes or that it doesn't come as long as the previous drought was, but suddenly, of course...
No, porque Dios quiera que no venga nunca la mala o que no venga tan larga como fue la sequía anterior, pero de repente, claro...
一支非常不败的球队，非常获胜，一个非常成功的周期，我想知道是否......
a very undefeated team, very winning, a very successful cycle and I was wondering if...
un equipo muy invicto, muy ganador, un ciclo muy exitoso y me preguntaba si...
让我们说，旧的，用引号引起来。
Let's say, the old ones, in quotes.
digamos, los viejos, entre comillas.
你好，莱昂内尔！
Hello, Leonel!
¡Ota, Leonel!
Fideo 存入了一个对他们来说非常糟糕的部分，直到他们取得成功，另一方面，你们年轻人带着直接的成功进入。
Fideo banked one that had a very bad part for them until they achieved that success, on the other hand, you young people enter with that direct success.
Fideo bancaron una que les tocó una parte muy mala hasta lograr ese éxito, en cambio ustedes los jóvenes entran con ese éxito directo.
我希望他永远不会来。
I hope he never comes.
Ojalá que no venga nunca.
至少就我而言，始终遵循这条道路和遗产......
At least on my part, always come and follow the path and the legacy that...
por lo menos de mi parte, siempre venir y seguir el camino y el legado que...
他们让我们完成了任务，带着同样的野心、同样的愿望继续前进，但这并没有给我们......
that they left us done, to continue with the same ambition, with the same desire, that it does not give us...
que nos dejaron hechos, seguir con la misma ambición, con la misma gana, que no nos dé...
我们不在乎穿这件衬衫，并始终以同样的热情和同样的愿望继续前进。
That we don't care about wearing this shirt and always continue with the same enthusiasm and the same desire.
que no nos dé igual vestir esta camiseta y siempre seguir con la misma ilusión y la misma gana.
赢得胜利，并且总是尽可能高地离开球队的愿望。
to win and that desire to always leave the team as high as possible.
de ganar y esa gana de dejar siempre la selección lo más alto posible.
例如，对于与你的游戏有关的事情、你可以进步的事情等等，你是否非常追求完美？
Are you very perfectionist, for example, with what has to do with your game, in the things you can progress and so on?
¿Sos muy perfeccionista, por ejemplo, con lo que tiene que ver con tu juego, en las cosas que podés progresar y eso?
放松，中间立场？
Relaxed, middle ground?
¿Relajado, término medio?
不，不，是，是。
No, no, yes, yes.
No, no, sí, sí.
我是说...
I mean...
O sea...
我非常喜欢自己。
I'm quite a fan of myself.
Soy bastante hinchabola conmigo mismo.
要求很高。
Demanding.
Exigente.
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
如果没有，显然我不喜欢它。
If not, obviously I don't like it.
Si no, obviamente no me gusta.
我不喜欢失败，我不喜欢……我不知道，就我而言……
I don't like losing, I don't like it... I don't know, in my case...
No me gusta perder, no me gusta... No sé, en mi caso...
努力取得好成绩，始终努力保持良好的位置。
Try to score well, always try to be well positioned.
Intentar marcar bien, intentar siempre estar bien parados.
当轮到我的时候，成为我同事的一个选择。
be an option for my colleagues when it's my turn.
ser una opción para mis compañeros cuando me toca.
这就是你获胜的地方，但有时也会留下苦涩的味道，因为事情并非如此。
That's where you win, but it leaves with a bitter taste sometimes, because things don't work out that way.
Por ahí se gana, pero se va con un sabor amargo a veces, que por ahí a uno no le salen las cosas.
在足球方面，有时你会变得更好，有时你会变得更差，但我对自己要求很高。
Football-wise, sometimes you get better, sometimes you get worse, but I am quite demanding of myself.
Fútbolamente a veces te sale mejor, a veces te sale peor, pero sí soy bastante exigente conmigo.
结束这个与年轻人的生活和老年人所见有关的话题。
to close this topic of what has to do with what the young lived and what the old saw.
para cerrar este tema de lo que tiene que ver con lo que vivieron los jóvenes y con lo que vieron los viejos.
有一个扣篮的时刻，奥塔、当时的费迪奥、梅西......
There is a moment of a dunk or something where Ota, Fideo at the time, Messi...
Hay un momento de una mateada o algo donde Ota, Fideo en su momento, Messi...
他们和你谈论这个吗？
Do they talk to you about this?
¿Les hablan a ustedes sobre esto?
伙计们，听着，这不正常，我们经历过糟糕的时光。
Guys, look, this is not normal, we have had bad times.
Chicos, miren que esto no es normal, nosotros pasamos las malas.
是否有某个时间进行这样的谈话？
Is there a time when that talk takes place?
¿Hay algún momento que se da esa charla?
它发生了吗？
Did it happen?
¿Se dio?
是的，是的，有苏格兰皇家银行或类似的东西，不是那么多，但更多。
Yes, yes, there has been RBS or something like that, not so much, but more so.
Sí, sí, se ha dado RBS o por ahí no tanto así, sino más.
更多的是记住我必须在国家队生活的时刻。
more of remembering moments that I had to live in the national team.
más del recordar momentos que yo les tocó vivir en la selección.
在这种情况下，我很保守，我自己不喜欢问太多。
And in that case I am quite reserved, I don't like to ask a lot myself.
Y en ese caso soy bastante reservado, no me gusta preguntar mucho a mí.
我不是一个会问很多问题的人，我只是注意他说的话，听他说。
I'm not one to ask a lot, I just pay attention to what he says, listening to him.
No soy de preguntar mucho, simplemente prestar atención en lo que dice, en escucharlo.
对我和每个人来说，能和狮子座在一起是一种荣幸。
For me and for everyone it is a privilege to be with Leo.
Para mí y para todos es un privilegio estar con Leo.
他不久前离开了我们，但我能够与他分享的那一刻令人难以置信。
He left us a little while ago, but the few moments I was able to share with him were incredible.
Se nos fue hace poquito, pero los pocos momentos que pude compartir con él fue increíble.
他总是对我说好话，给我建议，我几乎总是把他放在我面前，所以......
He always spoke well to me, he advised me, I almost always had him in front of me, so...
siempre me habló bien, me aconsejó, casi siempre lo tenía delante mío, así que...
只是和他聊天并总是帮助我，所以那是美好的时刻。
It was just chatting with him and always helping me, so they are nice moments.
Era charlar con él y siempre ayudándome, así que son lindos momentos.
他们可能问了你514次，我会选择515，尽量保持原创。
They probably asked you 514 times, I'm going to go with 515, try to be original.
Seguramente te lo preguntaron 514 veces, voy a ir con la 515, tratar de ser original.
在世界杯对阵荷兰队的比赛中，里奥给你的著名传球就是为了你的进球。
The famous pass that Leo gives you in the World Cup against Holland is for your goal.
El famoso pase que Leo te da en el Mundial contra Holanda es para tu gol.
让我们看看我这个问题是否原创。
Let's see if I'm original with the question.
A ver si soy original con la pregunta.
那一刻你就在你所在的位置
at that moment that you were in the location you were
en ese momento que vos estabas en la ubicación que estabas
你是否看到传球即将到来，或者你是否说这个人不可能从那里给我传球？
Do you see the pass coming or did you say it's impossible for this guy to give me a pass from there?
¿Vos ves venir el pase o dijiste es imposible que este chabón me de un pase desde ahí?
在那一秒？
In that second?
¿En ese segundo?
不，就在那一瞬间……
No, in that second...
No, en ese segundo...
我从来没有想到球会来到我身边。
I never imagined that the ball would come to me.
Nunca imaginé que me iba a venir a mí la pelota.
老实说，我发现自己的脚上有球。
Honestly, I found myself with the ball in my foot.
Sinceramente me encontré con la pelota en el pie.
因为你对他的角度……不，这已经不可能了。
Because the angle you had of him... No, it was already impossible.
Porque el ángulo que tenías de él... No, ya era imposible.
你不会从那里得到通行证。
You're not going to get a pass from there.
No vas a sacar un pase de ahí.
他已经不可能给我了。
It was already impossible for him to give it to me.
ya era imposible que me la dé.
是的，确实，前几次我都不得不停下来。
Yes, it is true that previous times I had to stop before.
Sí es verdad que anteriores veces me pasó de frenarme antes.
和他一起，或者和 Fide 一起，然后……
with him or with Fide and then...
con él o con Fide y que después...
这就是为什么我纠正他，继续跑。
That's why I corrected him, to keep running.
Por eso lo corregí, de seguir corriendo.
我总是坚持跑步，因为那...
I always kept running because that has that...
Siempre seguí corriendo porque eso tiene ese...
他们在最后一刻给你的王牌。
that ace up your sleeve that they give it to you at the last minute.
ese as bajo la manga que te la dan igual a último momento.
他们甚至可能告诉过你
They may even have told you
Incluso te habrán dicho vos
在某个时刻，球会到达你的身边。
that at some point the ball is going to reach you.
que en algún momento te va a llegar la pelota.
当然，我跟着你，因为他们直到最后一刻才照顾你的动作。
Of course, I followed you, because they take care of your movement until the last moment.
Claro, vos seguí, porque ellos cuidan hasta el último momento con tu movimiento.
所以在那一刻，为了以防万一你有疑问，你继续跑步。
So at that moment, just in case you were in doubt, you continued running.
O sea que en ese momento vos por las dudas seguiste corriendo.
我继续比赛，然后……
I continued the race and...
Yo seguí la carrera y...
我发现自己的脚上有球，幸运的是我也有时间快速上场。
I found myself with the ball on my foot and luckily I also had time to get my foot in quickly.
Me encontré con la pelota en el pie y por suerte me dio tiempo también de llegar a meter el pie rápido.
这是一个美丽的进球。
It was a beautiful goal.
Fue un golazo hermoso.
难以置信，世界四分之一决赛。
incredible, world quarterfinals.
increíble, cuartos finales mundiales.
这是你职业生涯中最美的时刻之一吗？
Is it one of the most beautiful of your career?
¿Es de los más lindos de tu carrera?
和。
And.
Si.
一定要选最喜欢的吗？
Do you have to choose the favorite?
¿Tienes que elegir el favorito?
最大。
The maximum.
Lo máximo.
成为世界杯冠军后，表现最好的。
After becoming champion in the World Cup, the best.
Después de salir campeón en el Mundial, lo máximo.
进球。
Score a goal.
Hacer un gol.
后面就没有那么多的可能性了。
right back there doesn't have as many possibilities.
lateral derecho por ahí no tiene tantas posibilidades.
到了之后就更加看剧了。
arriving and then looking at the play even more.
de llegar y después mirando la jugada más todavía.
塔利亚菲科说我们必须组建双方联盟。
Tagliafico says that we have to form a union of the sides.
Tagliafico dice que hay que hacer el gremio de los laterales.
我问他是左还是右，他说不是，大家团结。
I asked him if left or right, he said no, all united.
Le pregunté si izquierdo o derecho, me dijo no, todos unidos.
我们必须这样做。
And we would have to do it like this.
Y tendríamos que hacerlo así.
公会由什么组成？
What would the guild consist of?
¿De qué constaría el gremio?
侧向联合有什么用？
What is the laterals union for?
¿Para qué sirve el gremio de laterales?
聚在一起，看看我们有多少人，因为我们很少。
To get together, to see how many we are, because we are few.
Para juntarnos, para ver cuántos somos, porque somos pocos.
听我说。
Listen to me.
Escúchame.
纹身主题。
Tattoo theme.
Tema tatuaje.
我不清楚。
I'm not clear.
No tengo clara.
让我们看看，告诉我这个故事。
Let's see, tell me the story.
A ver, contame la historia.
全部选择。
All selection.
Todo selección.
美洲杯回来了。
Copa America back.
Copa América atrás.
第一届美洲杯。
Copa América the first.
Copa América la primera.
那里有日期，然后是世界杯。
that has the date there, then a World Cup.
que tiene la fecha ahí, después un Mundial.
理想的 12-18-22 完美搭配盾牌和这个
ideal 12-18-22 perfect with the shield and this
ideal 18-12-22 perfecto con el escudo y este
非常最终的，这是与...的承诺
very final and this was the promise with...
finalísima y este que fue la promesa con...
还有总是在场的 Cuti 和 Licha。
with Cuti and Licha who are the ones who are always there.
con Cuti y Licha que son los que estamos siempre ahí.
决赛那天我们没有谈论任何承诺。
On the day of the final we had not talked about promises, about anything.
El día de la final no habíamos hablado nada de promesas, de nada.
决赛当天，早上喝马黛茶。
on the day of the final, in the morning drinking mate.
el día de la final, a la mañana tomando mate.
思考可能发生的一切。
thinking about everything that could happen.
pensando en todo lo que podía llegar a pasar.
这是在卡塔尔，决赛之前。
This in Qatar, before the final.
Esto en Qatar, previo a la final.
是的，是的，决赛那天。
Yes, yes, the day of the final.
Sí, sí, el día de la final.
如果我们成为冠军，他们会怎么说？
And what do they say if we become champions?
¿Y qué dicen si salimos campeones?
如果我们成为冠军，我们三个人都会纹身。
If we become champions, all three of us will tattoo them.
Si salimos campeones, los tatuamos los tres.
你知道这会是那张他们三人背后的照片吗？
Did you know it was going to be that photo, the three of them from behind?
¿Sabían que iba a ser esa foto, los tres de espaldas?
然后它就被创建了。
Then it was created.
Después se fue creando.
因为是库蒂先做的，而且我们非常喜欢它。
Because Cuti did it first and we liked it so much.
Porque primero se lo hizo el Cuti y nos gustó tanto.
好吧，创建了一个......
And well, there was created a...
Y bueno, ahí se fue creando un...
它是用不同的照片创建的。
With different photos it was created.
con distintas fotos se fue creando.
不，不，显然是对他纹身的纹身师。
No, no, obviously with the tattoo artist who did it to him.
No, no, obviamente con el tatuador que se lo hizo él.
我们比库蒂更信任纹身师，对吧？
We trust the tattoo artist more than Cuti, right?
Confiamos más en el tatuador que en Cuti, ¿no?
这不是纹身艺术家Cuti的艺术部分。
It is not the art part of the tattoo artist Cuti.
No es la parte del arte el tatuador Cuti.
美好的回忆，我们三个人分享了美好的事情。
A nice memory, the three of us have shared nice things.
Un lindo recuerdo, hemos compartido cosas lindas los tres.
作为一个男孩，他和Licha一起踢防守，我们已经来了很长时间了，这是他的20岁了。
As a boy, with Licha he played defense, we have been coming for a long time, it is his 20th.
de chico, con Licha jugó en defensa, veníamos hace tiempo, es su 20.
所以很高兴继续。
so it was nice to continue.
así que fue hermoso seguir.
一起继续这条道路，目前我们进展顺利。
continue this path together and for now we continue well.
seguir este camino juntos y que por ahora seguimos bien.
有很多cordobesiada。
There is a lot of cordobesiada.
Hay mucha cordobesiada.
我也是来自卡洛斯帕斯，不知道你是否知道。
I'm from Carlos Paz too, I don't know if you know.
Yo soy de Carlos Paz también, no sé si sabés.
库蒂和你之间。
between Cuti and you.
entre Cuti y vos.
团队里还有更多科尔多瓦人吗？
Are there more Cordobans on the team?
¿Hay más Cordobés en el equipo?
还有……嗯，巴勃罗、朱莉……
And there is... Well, Pablo, Juli...
Y está... Bueno, Pablo, Juli...
维瓦拉、帕布利托·艾马尔……
Vivala, Pablito Aymar...
但有一种科尔多贝斯式的时刻，就像你听到酒吧里最后一声一样
but there is a cordobesian moment like did you hear the last one from the bar
pero hay un momento cordobesiado tipo escuchaste el último de la barra
你听说过美味。
You heard Tasty.
Escuchaste Sabroso.
四重奏没有。
Quartet no.
Cuarteto no.
显然，我们听四重奏，但没有……
We listen to Quartet, obviously, but no...
Escuchamos Cuarteto, obviamente, pero no...
至少对我而言，已经迷失了一半。
It's half lost, at least on my part.
Está medio perdido, por lo menos de mi parte.
我来自科尔多瓦，没有人能把它从我身边夺走。
I'm from Córdoba and no one can take it from me.
Soy cordobés y no me lo saca nadie.
我很小的时候就离开了，11 岁时就离开了 Embalse，好吧，我也花了很多时间在外面，所以......
I left when I was very young, I left Embalse when I was 11 and well, I spent a lot of time outside too, so...
Me fui de muy chico, yo me fui a los 11 años de Embalse y bueno, mucho tiempo afuera también, así que...
我的部分是中间的一半。
My part is half in the middle.
Mi parte está medio en el medio.
谁才是最能保持科尔多瓦精髓的人呢？
Who would be the one who maintains the most Cordoban essence?
¿Quién sería el que mantiene la esencia más cordobesa?
我正在度假。
I'm on holiday.
El cuti.
也就是说，我们可以给小可爱一只装有古柯的雪貂，我们可以让他听四重奏，他坚持说。
That is, we can give the cuti a fernet with coca, we can make him listen to a quartet, he maintains.
O sea, el cuti le podemos dar un fernet con coca, le podemos hacer escuchar un cuarteto, mantiene.
是的，因为我认为他是在科尔多瓦呆的时间最长的人。
Yes, because I think he was the one who spent the longest time in Córdoba.
Sí, porque fue creo que el que más tiempo también estuvo en Córdoba.
当然，当然。
Of course, of course.
Claro, claro.
因为他总是在贝尔格拉诺踢球，所以他总是在那里踢球。
Because he always played there in Belgrano, he always played there.
Porque jugó siempre ahí en Belgrano, siempre jugó ahí.
听着，纳韦尔，你想走多远？
Listen, Nahuel, and how far would you like to go?
Escucha, Nahuel, ¿y hasta dónde te gustaría llegar?
你有什么志向？
What ambitions do you have?
¿Qué ambiciones tenés?
你说呢，我现在已经在国家队和俱乐部取得了很多成就，你的梦想是什么？
What do you say, well, I've already achieved a lot with the national team now, with the clubs, what do you dream of?
¿Qué cosa decís, bueno ya, ya logré mucho con la selección ahora, con los clubes, con qué soñás?
不。
No.
显然，在俱乐部层面。
At club level, obviously.
A nivel club, obviamente.
我一直梦想着获胜，继续为国家队和俱乐部赢得胜利。
I always dreamed of winning, of continuing to win with the national team and with the club.
Siempre tuve soñar con ganar, con seguir ganando con la selección y con el club.
我们之前谈论过一些关于Leo、国际棋联留给我们的东西，以及始终有继续前进并想要获胜的使命。
a little bit what we were talking about before about what Leo, FIDE left us and always having the mission to continue and want to win.
un poco lo que hablábamos antes de lo que nos dejaron Leo, el FIDE y siempre tener la misión de seguir y querer ganar.
显然在俱乐部层面我就没那么幸运了。
Obviously at the club level I wasn't so lucky.
Obviamente a nivel club por ahí no tuve tanta suerte.
但始终怀着实现这一目标的希望。
but always with the hope of achieving it.
pero siempre con la ilusión de conseguirlo.
重要的冠军联赛冠军联赛将是......
The important title, Champions League, would be...
El título importante, Champions League, sería...
这对于国家队来说显然也是一件美妙的事情。
It would be something beautiful and obviously with the national team as well.
Sería algo hermoso y obviamente con la selección también.
当我小的时候，我是一些世界级俱乐部的球迷，对吧？
And when I was little I was a fan of some world-class club, right?
Y de chiquito era fan así de algún club de hablo mundial, ¿no?
马德里、巴塞罗那……您是其中某个人的忠实粉丝吗？
Madrid, Barcelona... Were you a big fan of anyone in particular?
Madrid, Barcelona... ¿Eras como muy seguidor de alguno en especial?
不，我会告诉你巴塞罗那是因为利奥，因为它在阿根廷代表的一切。
No, I would tell you Barcelona because of Leo, because of everything it represented here in Argentina.
No, te diría Barcelona por Leo, por todo lo que representaba acá en Argentina.
但他没有狂热。
but he didn't have a fanaticism.
pero no tenía un fanatismo.
每天就是踢足球，仅此而已。
It was playing football every day and nothing more.
Era jugar al fútbol todos los días y nada más.
当你不再踢足球时会发生什么？
And what will happen when you don't play football anymore?
¿Y qué va a pasar cuando no juegues más al fútbol?
还缺少很多东西。
There's a lot missing.
Falta un montón.
缺乏运气，但你必须...我不知道，老实说不...
Lack of luck, but you have to... I don't know, honestly not...
Falta suerte, pero hay que... No sé, sinceramente no...
没有其他活动可以说...不，目前我还没有考虑过它，我想...
There is no other activity that you can say... No, for now I haven't thought about it and I think...
No hay otra actividad que digas... No, por ahora no lo he pensado y creo que...
如果我现在再想这样的事情，那就大错特错了。
It would be a mistake for me to think of something like that now.
sería un error de parte mía pensar en algo así ahora.
我更喜欢专注于我所拥有的，享受......
I prefer to stay focused on what I have, enjoy...
prefiero mantenerme enfocado en lo que tengo, disfrutar de...
迄今为止我所取得的一切，以及今天在马德里竞技队所享受的一切。
of everything I have achieved so far, of enjoying today at Atlético de Madrid.
de todo lo que conseguí hasta ahora, de disfrutar hoy en Atlético de Madrid.
一个令人难以置信的俱乐部，所以我每次来到国家队都很享受。
An incredible club, so I enjoy every time I get to come to the national team.
Un club increíble, así que disfrutar cada vez que me toque venir a la selección.
来自我的家人、我的女朋友等等。
from my family, from my girlfriend and more than that.
de mi familia, de mi novia y más que eso.
如果我的想法超出了这个范围，那就错了。
It would be a mistake for me to think beyond that.
sería un error para mí pensar más allá.
你们有非常好的技术人员，斯卡罗尼、乔洛，还有很好的队友。
You have very good technicians, Scaloni, Cholo, good teammates.
tenés muy buenos técnicos, Scaloni, el Cholo, buenos compañeros.
在我看来，马竞是一家我内部并不了解的俱乐部。
Atleti seems to me to be a club that I don't know internally.
El Atleti me parece que es un club que no conozco internamente.
地狱，可以说，非常好。
Hell, let's say, very good.
De la hostia, digamos, buenísimo.
你提到了你的女朋友，我不知道你们交往多久了，但我想知道是否...
You mentioned your girlfriend, I don't know how long you've been dating, but I wanted to know if...
Mencionaste a tu novia, no sé cuándo hace que estás de novio, pero quería saber si...
你浪漫吗？
Are you romantic?
¿Sos romántico?
不，一点点，一点点。
No, little, little.
No, poco, poco.
少量。
Bit.
Poco.
很少。
Very little.
Muy poco.
谁说是的？
Who said it was?
¿Quién dijo que era?
塔利亚说他很浪漫。
Thalia said he was very romantic.
Thalia dijo que era muy romántico él.
比新娘还要多。
More than the bride.
Más que la novia.
老师。
teacher.
profesor.
他说的是横向公会吗？
Did he talk about the lateral guild?
¿Del gremio lateral este habló?
不，不，这对我来说更难。
No, no, it's harder for me.
No, no, a mí me cuesta más.
我很内向。
I am very undemonstrative.
Soy muy poco demostrativo.
不仅是和她，还有我的家人。
Not only with her, but with my family.
No solo con ella, sino con mi familia.
尽管我和她已经有九年的关系了。
although with the relationship I have had with her for nine years.
si bien con la relación que tengo con ella hace nueve años.
我们在一起的空间很小。
It's very small that we are together.
Es muy chico que estamos juntos.
我开放了一点，但我非常封闭。
I opened up a little, but I am very closed.
Fui abriéndome un poco, pero soy muy cerrado.
你说我爱你，我的爱人。
You say I love you, my love.
Le tirás un te amo, mi amor.
是的，嗯，是的。
Yes, well, yes.
Sí, bueno, eso sí.
卡帕诺，你是那个感到惊讶的人。
Capano, you are the one with the surprise.
Capano, sos el de la sorpresa.
不，不，写封信，不。
No, no, write a letter, no.
No, no, escribir una carta, no.
一朵花？
A flower?
¿Una flor?
礼物？
A gift?
¿Un regalo?
不。
No.
香水？
A perfume?
¿Un perfumito?
礼物是的，但是……
A gift yes, but...
Un regalo sí, pero...
但这让我付出了代价。
but it costs me.
pero me cuesta.
你很难敞开心扉。
It's hard for you to open up.
Te cuesta abrirte.
这也是友情级别的吗？
Is that on a friendship level too?
¿Eso a nivel amistad también?
是的，在各个方面。
Yes, in every way.
Si, en todos sentidos.
他害羞还是矜持？
Is he shy or reserved?
¿Es tímido o reservado?
预订的。
Reserved.
Reservado.
对我来说很难...
It's hard for me...
Me cuesta...
敞开心扉一点感性。
open up a little with the sentimental.
abrirme un poco con lo sentimental.
你很难放手，这个词是什么？
It's hard for you to let go. What's the word?
Te cuesta soltarte ¿Cuál es la palabra?
这将定义成为世界冠军的感觉。
that would define the feeling of being world champion.
que definiría el sentimiento de ser campeón del mundo.
你会选择什么词？
What word would you choose?
¿Qué palabra elegirías?
感觉选项。
Feel options.
Sentir opciones.
骄傲、幸福、喜悦。
Pride, happiness, joy.
Orgullo, felicidad, alegría.
不，是幸福。
No, happiness.
No, felicidad.
绝对的幸福。
Absolute happiness.
Felicidad absoluta.
至少和其他东西没有可比性
It has no comparison with anything else at least
no tiene comparación con otra cosa por lo menos
就我而言，我还不是一个父亲，所以其他有孩子的人可能会说，但不是。
In my case, I'm not a dad yet, so someone else who has children might say, but no.
En mi caso no soy papá todavía así que por ahí otro que tenga hijos podría decir, pero no.
我想这就是绝对的幸福。
I think it is absolute happiness.
creo que es felicidad absoluta.
我不想忘记这个。
I don't want to forget this one.
No me quiero olvidar de esta.
您与 NL 俱乐部有很多共同之处。
You share a lot with NL Club.
Compartís mucho con NL Club.
谁的造型最时尚？
Who has the most fashionable looks?
¿Quién tira más facha moda?
¿罗德里·德波尔还是埃洛塔？
¿Rodri de Pol or Elota?
¿Rodri de Pol o Elota?
我每天都会有更多的罗德里，我时不时也会看到另一个，但他们俩都是一场精彩的战斗。
And I have Rodri more on a day-to-day basis, I see another from time to time, but both of them, it's a good fight.
Y a Rodri lo tengo más en el día a día, a otra lo veo cada tanto, pero los dos, es una buena pelea.
这是一场很好的战斗，不是吗？
It's a good fight, isn't it?
Es una buena pelea, ¿no?
他们是两个最堕落的人。
They are the two most fallonists.
Son los dos más fallonistas.
是的，是的，是的。
Yes, yes, yes.
Sí, sí, sí.
他们是两个...
They are the two that...
Son los dos que...
我想说，谁最关心。
who care the most, I would say.
que más se preocupan, diría.
但是哦，多么困难啊。
But oh, how difficult.
Pero, uy, qué difícil.
我会对罗德里说，因为我每天都会有更多的他。
I would say to Rodri, because I have him more on a daily basis.
A Rodri diría, porque lo tengo más en el día a día.
是的，如果他不打算责备你的话。
Yes, if he's not going to reproach you.
Sí, si no te va a recriminar.
他会看到这张纸条并指责你。
He's going to see the note and he's going to recriminate you.
Va a ver la nota y te va a recriminar.
最后，理想的肉末。
Last, ideal minced meat.
Última, picadito ideal.
你必须把自己和生活中的其他四个人放在一起。
You have to put together yourself and four others in life.
Tienes que armar vos y cuatro más de la vida.
你可以选择梅西，你的表弟，无论是谁。
You can choose Messi, your cousin, whoever.
Podes elegir a Messi, a tu primo, el que sea.
无论谁来，陪你对战的四个人是谁？
Who are the four that accompany you to play against whoever comes?
¿Quiénes son los cuatro que te acompañan para jugar contra el que venga?
不。
No.
为了比赛我必须击败Ciosito。
And to play I have to beat Ciosito.
Y para jugar tengo que ganar a Ciosito.
选择其他四个，这就是原因。
Choosing the other four, that's why.
Elegir a los otros cuatro, por eso.
致迪沃·拉科。
To Divo Larco.
Al Divo Larco.
我有比赛，有防守，我从头到尾读着，然后我们让他放松了。
I have play, defense, I read from the top of my head and we let him loose.
Yo tengo jugada, defensa, leo de mente arriba y lo dejamos suelto.
国际棋联。
FIDE.
完美，我们会把它拿出来。
Perfect, we'll take it out.
Perfecto, lo sacamos en retiro.
我缺一个。
I'm missing one.
Me falta uno.
当然，还有一个在你后面玩的人。
And one who plays behind with you, of course.
Y uno que juega atrás con vos, claro.
也就是说，Fideo 和 Leo 向上，Divo 向下，你和还有谁。
That is, Fideo and Leo up, Divo the bow, you and who else.
O sea, Fideo y Leo arriba, Divo el arco, vos y quién más.
我们完成了五个。
And we complete the five.
Y completamos los cinco.
我会说库蒂和利查，他们两个在后面，我出去互相拥抱。
And I would say Cuti and Licha, the two of them in the back and I go out and hug each other.
Y diría Cuti y Licha, los dos atrás y yo salgo y abrazado.
你才六年级，伙计。
You're in sixth grade, man.
Vos te ponés de sexto, hombre.
我做烧烤，让它获胜。
I make the barbecue, let that win.
Yo hago el asado, que eso lo gane.
朋友，非常感谢我们的官方伙伴和潘帕朋友送给您的这份礼物。
Friend, I thank you very much for this gift from our official mate and pampa friends to you.
amigo te agradezco muchísimo este regalo de nuestros amigos de mate y pampa oficiales para vos
显然是来自国家队，显然是来自世界冠军。
Obviously it's from the national team and obviously it's from the world champions.
Obviamente es de la selección y obviamente es de los campeones del mundo.
这太棒了，是市场上最好的，他们把这一切都分解了。
It's great, the best on the market, they break it all down.
Está buenísimo, lo mejor del mercado, la rompen toda.
灰狗。
Greyhound.
Agárralo.
它有旗帜。
It has the flag.
Tiene la banderita.
太感谢了。
Thank you so much.
Muchas gracias.
你喜欢我吗？
You like me?
¿Te gustó?
是的。
Yeah.
Sí.
世界领域。
Field of the World.
Campo del Mundo.
¡ 壮观！
¡Pectacular!
我喜欢它。
I love it.
A mí me encanta.
多谢。
Thanks a lot.
Muchísimas gracias.
我喜欢这个，因为我喜欢那面小旗帜和浅蓝色的一切，非常壮观。
I love this one because I love the little flag and everything in light blue, spectacular.
Me encanta este porque me encanta la banderita y todo en celeste, espectacular.
纳韦尔，非常感谢你。
Nahuel, thank you very much.
Nahuel, muchas gracias.
非常友善。
Very kind.
Muy amable.
很高兴认识你。
Pleased to meet you.
Un placer conocerte.
感谢您的良好氛围。
Thanks for the good vibes.
Gracias por la buena onda.
这是一个现象，爸爸要小心。
This is a phenomenon, watch out for Daddy.
Este es un fenómeno, ojo con Daddy.
爸爸，请伸出有力的手，那...
Put a strong hand, Daddy, that...
Mete mano fuerte, Daddy, que...
尼科·诺韦洛，按下，破解。
Nico Novello, press, crack.
Nico Novello, prensa, crack.
已经在 Infobae 的老爹下了大力气。
The Daddy, who was already in Infobae, puts in a strong hand.
El Daddy, que ya estuvo en Infobae, mete mano fuerte.
什么时候需要按摩？
When do you have to massage?
cuando tiene que masajear?
我不知道，他在那里享有特权。
I don't know, he is privileged there.
No sé, él tiene privilegiado ahí.
你不会得到下一张。
You don't get the next one.
No te toca el seguido.
我没有收到下一张。
I didn't get the next one.
No me tocó el seguido.
呃，爸爸，卡卡斯特。
Uy, Daddy, cagaste.
我们必须解决这个问题，爸爸。
We have to fix this situation, Daddy.
Hay que arreglar esta situación, Daddy.
这对你来说会很昂贵。
This is going to be expensive for you.
Te va a salir caro esto.
幸运的是，我们在选择方面拥有非常优秀的专业人士。
Luckily we have very good professionals in the selection.
Por suerte tenemos muy buenos profesionales en la selección.
显然，这对我们很有帮助。
Which serves us very well, obviously.
Que nos atiende muy bien, obviamente.
他从展位出来，看看他如何给你角度。
He came out of the booth, look how he gives you the angle.
Salió de reservado, mira cómo te da el ángulo.
兄弟，你是不是在说谎？
Brother, are you telling any lies?
Hermano, ¿alguna mentira estás diciendo?
再见纳韦尔，谢谢现象。
Bye Nahuel, thank you phenomenon.
Chau Nahuel, gracias fenómeno.
Nahuel Molina，Infobah de Random，AFA 特别精选。
Nahuel Molina, here at Infobah de Random, special AFA Selection.
Nahuel Molina, aquí en Infobah de Random, especial AFA Selección.